{
    "id": "5713a324e79a48aba84b815bdfa58190",
    "title": "Complete The Given Passage",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "India .....................…… with many historical places and monuments.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "studded",
                "is studding",
                "is studded"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "23e9d5be1d304aeba50b5368687d685c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Agra ……………. an important place among them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occupy",
                "occupies",
                "is occupied"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "74c2643e82fe4957ae9b6740c44c33ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "The famous Taj Mahal ………………. this city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is immortalizing",
                "had immortalized",
                "has immortalized"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2e9daaea92fa45818f10017a9aff0006"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was my long cherished dream to visit Taj Mahal and it ..................... last month when the school ..................... a trip to Agra.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fulfilled, organized",
                "has fulfilled, organized",
                "was fulfilled, organized"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b50c92d867d44b4eb9deb41f25b83c5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Taj Mahal ....................... one of the most famous buildings in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d4d7319704374ab8a5ce71c381c515fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "It .......................... situated on the River Yamuna.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "was",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7411f5641ee54753a352d8466d3ad537"
        },
        {
            "question": "Its four minarets, the tombs and the white marble ...................... it the most beautiful building in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "makes",
                "is making"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2b2557eb7b3a4230a6f22eef6a6d8e48"
        },
        {
            "question": "Poets ..................... it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had praised",
                "have praised"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26110c37053944a0bc0bdaec46365942"
        },
        {
            "question": "Common people ..................... it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adore",
                "adorn",
                "adoring"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a378702f723a4d4f85d920f43ddd7464"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lovers of art from all over the world ......................... it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "visiting",
                "were visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "71f1935cffab49a9a7beaf86fc084915"
        }
    ]
}